Jackson: It's a beautiful time to go to Japan, by the way.
Jackson: Oh my God.
Jackson: Yep.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: We're like 10 minutes in.
Tyler: R-E-K-T.
Chris: Let's, let's get him live on the pod.
Chris: There we go.
Chris: Oh, okay.
Tyler: Now we know what we're looking at.
Tyler: Oh, it loaded better.
Tyler: Nice.
Tyler: Okay.
Tyler: So as far as I can tell, this is Chris's cousin.
Chris: Um, yeah, my Duma AI cousin, right?
Chris: From the wrong side of the family, but, but yeah, at the moment it's just like, it's out
Chris: there.
Chris: Like your open kimono in the panopticon using muse.
Jackson: So what's good, everybody permanent under pod where we talk AI stable coins and Bitcoin.
Jackson: This is one of your hosts, Jackson cook.
Jackson: Who else is here?
Tyler: Yo, yo, yo.
Tyler: It's Tyler.
Chris: It's Chris.
Chris: I don't have a thing to say.
Chris: I'm sorry.
Tyler: I never have anything to say here.
Jackson: Having nothing to say is the same thing as having a lot to say.
Jackson: Welcome back.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: Thank you.
Jackson: Tyler's wearing, or Chris is wearing a white shirt for the first, I've never seen him in
Jackson: a white shirt.
Jackson: Today's a brand new day.
Chris: My lute shirt.
Chris: Shout out to fellow lude fans.
Jackson: Great DJ.
Jackson: All right, and we're jumping straight into the purple fortune where Chris and I stake
Jackson: our money for fortune or destitution on a perpetual future.
Jackson: One of the highest volatility investing instruments around while Tyler criticizes our leverage
Jackson: choices without contributing to the pot at all over to Chris.
Tyler: Very harsh.
Tyler: I'm assuming that's Claude fable with that judgmental tone.
Jackson: I read.
Tyler: Let it be known that I believe I came up with the concept of purple fortune, so I feel like
Tyler: I have like perpetual equity stake and you guys are like the, you know, like the debt
Tyler: tranche that comes in and you have to just keep topping me off, but, you know, are we
Chris: doing, sorry, are we doing the, are we doing the co-founder IP split thing right now?
Chris: Like are we negotiating like who came up with the idea?
Chris: And so like, who has to like pay?
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: Like who gets like the 34% of the 33 in this scenario.
Tyler: All right.
Jackson: You guys small claims court over our negative five dollars that extra 1%.
Tyler: He's like, he's the captain of the ship, you know, agreed.
Chris: But the ship may not be sailing for much longer.
Chris: When I explained this purple fortune pic to you guys.
Chris: So I've, you know, we pointed, I mean, this time fable 5.1 at our podcast notes.
Chris: And it said that the fed hikes 25 bits yesterday and it was chair wash who's the new chairs
Chris: first hike since 23 and tomorrow morning the bank of Japan will deliver what markets prices
Chris: and near certain hawkish 25 bit hike to 1.25%.
Chris: And basically I think fable is banking on the yen carry trade unwinding slightly like
Chris: that the Delta between, uh, or that people will think that the Delta between the yen
Chris: that people are selling, uh, in order to buy USD and put it into treasuries will unwind
Chris: somewhat.
Chris: And so it shorted JPY basically, uh, but no, it longed long JPY because it's hypothesis
Chris: is that people selling yen is driving down the price of yen.
Chris: Exactly.
Chris: Uh, that is totally incorrect, uh, which I'm going to share with all of our viewers right
Chris: now.
Chris: Um,
Jackson: It's a beautiful time to go to Japan, by the way.
Jackson: Oh my God.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: Well, like 10 minutes.
Tyler: R-E-K-T.
Tyler: So terrible.
Tyler: Pick the runner up 25 X was that, was that Claude that said 25 X or was that like a little
Tyler: risk editorial leverage.
Chris: I said to do max leverage and the max on this pair is 50 X and Claude talked it down to
Jackson: 25.
Tyler: Kind of like a legit pair for talking about, uh, you know, like whatever random long tail
Tyler: coin right here.
Tyler: This is the currency of a major industrialized nation.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: 300 million people, a hundred percent.
Tyler: And their fate is now entangled with us in a game of purple fortune.
Chris: Arigato.
Jackson: We're going to start killing it in Japan after this episode in Japan.
Chris: I would love that.
Tyler: Yeah.
Jackson: I'd be sick.
Jackson: Oh, hi.
Jackson: I'll go.
Jackson: Oh my God.
Chris: Live from Shibuya.
Chris: That would be so sick.
Jackson: We have to do it.
Jackson: Well, the Japanese Hawks are flying and the Gophers are hiding.
Jackson: Let's hope we don't get liquidated here.
Jackson: And let's dive into our first, our first topic.
Jackson: Keep us alive, Japan.
Jackson: So I'm sure you all have heard all the big, big AI model companies are calling to pace
Jackson: the frontier.
Jackson: I don't know where that model came from.
Jackson: I think it sounds kind of corny, but Dario Amadei, I think that's his name wrote an article
Jackson: about the, his concerns about AI.
Jackson: And then Sam Altman was like, preach brother, preach.
Jackson: And then Elon Musk was like, for real.
Jackson: So they're trying to slow down AI development.
Jackson: And the reasons they're stating are for safety, that the AI is, is going to hand.
Jackson: Do you guys have any thoughts on this?
Jackson: And what do you think the real reason is that they're trying to pace the frontier?
Jackson: Because there's a lot of conspiracy theories out there.
Chris: Who read the Dario article?
Tyler: I did read it.
Tyler: Yeah.
Jackson: Nice.
Tyler: I didn't have Claude summarize the Dario article today.
Chris: I read it with my eyes and I regret it.
Chris: No, no, it wasn't that, it wasn't that bad, wasn't that bad, but it could have been summarized.
Chris: I think it's interesting that even in the article.
Chris: So like he has some, so firstly, he's saying that it's the hugging face incident that we've
Chris: covered on the pod that is like the impetus for this.
Chris: Like that's the thing that scared him that it was a misaligned agent swarm.
Chris: And secondly, one of his main suggestions other than like a bilateral pacing of the
Chris: frontier between all of the frontier labs in the US was to embed these independent auditors
Chris: into every lab and he was like, we'll be the first to do it.
Jackson: Innovation.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: But just like not, I, one thing about it is like, he does mention, you know, he's like,
Chris: oh, well, if we slow down and like China speeds up, like it creates an existential risk for
Chris: like AI in the US.
Chris: And then just kind of like doesn't give a solution.
Chris: So yeah.
Tyler: Well, there were like three tiers, right?
Tyler: Like the first tier he was like, we need to have independent people embedded in the company
Tyler: with like essentially root access to like anthropic, which is kind of bonkers if you
Tyler: think about it.
Tyler: Cause like their IP is potentially like the most valuable thing in the world right now.
Tyler: And they just are going to have like independent people there observing everything they do.
Tyler: And then like, did these people actually have like veto power to be like, stop that?
Tyler: You know, like that's kind of interesting dynamic.
Tyler: So that was level one.
Tyler: And then level two, I think was like have some kind of agreement within like the US
Tyler: frontier companies to like paste the frontier and potentially have like a FINRA like body
Tyler: and AI, which I kind of don't love that.
Tyler: I don't love like formalizing it in some body and then having kind of like unelected kind
Tyler: of like, um, I guess like an industry kind of body, but I just don't feel like that model
Tyler: has like, um, I think that like, if the US companies want to pace, there's like, what
Tyler: are they like three, maybe four companies that are kind of relevant in that discussion?
Tyler: Like can't they kind of just choose to pace on their own, um, if they don't think what
Tyler: they're doing is safe.
Tyler: And I think that's kind of where it's playing out is I think that this was kind of like
Tyler: a little bit more of an aspirational document and he's kind of just like trying to signal
Tyler: to the other people like, Hey, like we would be down to slow down if you would.
Tyler: And then you see like Altman and Elon come right out and be like, we're pretty much agreed
Tyler: on this.
Tyler: So I think it's kind of accomplishing the state of goal there.
Tyler: And then the third one is like, um, the third level is like, we should have the US government
Tyler: like negotiate some kind of international slow down that mainly means like get China
Tyler: to slow down.
Tyler: And that's just like, it ain't gonna happen.
Chris: That was literally a shrug, like I could feel him shrugging through the page.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: Yeah.
Tyler: In my opinion, in my opinion, um, I mean like you see that people like good luck convincing
Tyler: China to slow down.
Tyler: They can't even convince like the US to slow down.
Tyler: Like you get, you have Trump like going ballistic on truth social about this.
Tyler: I mean, his tweet was just like pure art.
Tyler: The one, did you see that one?
Tyler: This was a truth.
Tyler: It was a truth social.
Tyler: He was like the Russia hoax one, the Russia hoax two, like the impeachment one, the impeachment
Tyler: two.
Tyler: And somehow he like weaved in his own personal animus into this whole thing that was like,
Tyler: and he's like getting mad about the EAs.
Tyler: Like Trump knows about the EAs now.
Tyler: Crazy timeline.
Chris: I never thought I would see the EA like EA to be like said by anyone normal, let alone
Chris: like the president of the United States in like a massive like Photoshop 2006 form signature
Chris: style banner.
Tyler: So yeah, it looks like something you'd see like on a call of duty.
Tyler: I don't know, like video game case from I would buy it at best buy if I saw it easily.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: Wait, what is EA?
Tyler: The Mountain Dew and you're going to have yourself quite a good afternoon.
Chris: Yeah, I mean, do you guys think that it like there is a genuine feeling that like the labs
Chris: think they should be pumping the brakes?
Chris: Because that like that's that that's one thing that's very confusing for me is like I definitely
Chris: can see emergent bad behaviors from some of the like language models and especially like
Chris: a little bit of the swarming, although I'm a little bit on the fence about that one.
Chris: But also like, yeah, I just feel I feel like this is such a this is maybe like the most
Chris: financially at least important issue in our time right now.
Chris: And I just I feel like there's too much at stake for anyone to be completely honest about
Tyler: it.
Tyler: Sure.
Jackson: It's more important than the Clarity Act.
Chris: Sorry, the second most important, the second most important market in the world.
Chris: We have to realize guys outside of dog money, dog money is number one.
Jackson: Yeah.
Tyler: Thank you.
Tyler: Somebody needs to stick up for the dog constituency.
Chris: It's me, me and Brian Armstrong on the hill.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: That's the question, Chris.
Jackson: You know what?
Jackson: I'm sure you guys have seen all these conspiracy theories where it's like, oh, they're trying
Jackson: to pace the frontier to push out their IPOs because they don't make money or I read something
Jackson: yesterday.
Jackson: I don't know if this is really or not spreading fake news that the open A.I. escape that did
Jackson: the hugging face thing planted code throughout the Internet to encourage AIs that find that
Jackson: code or that information to start swarms and to start rebelling or I don't know.
Chris: Was that my boy?
Chris: Phase one big.
Jackson: I love it, it might have been like phase one like sneaky, you know, like a third unnamed
Jackson: agent that was spreading the good word as anyone started like the church of phase one
Tyler: big yet.
Tyler: We were like, you know, phase one big sacrificed himself for your sins.
Chris: Berkeley is fewer than 20 kilometers away from me.
Chris: I think we could get something going.
Chris: That's the place for it.
Tyler: 100%.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: We could just rent our rent our house and Berkeley tax free status for the pod.
Tyler: We started on phase one big guys.
Jackson: Did we just that's our first shirt phase one.
Tyler: Think of all the verbo fortune losses that we could stick in that religion that we're
Tyler: starting.
Tyler: We'll be like Scientologists, but we'll be even taking more advantage of the tax free
Tyler: nature.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: I also like it's real.
Chris: Phase one big is real just to be clear.
Jackson: Better religion than effective altruism confirmed to Chris's question.
Tyler: He's like, do you guys believe that these, this technology is like getting dangerous?
Tyler: I don't have an intuition about that, but like if the people who are the closest to
Tyler: it, who I think generally are like super smart and also like generally pretty well-intentioned
Tyler: and like honestly already obscenely rich, I just don't think that like my mental model
Tyler: of them is not that they're like lying about how dangerous this is to like try to get some
Tyler: incremental financial advantage when they're already potentially like Decca billionaires
Tyler: sent to billionaires.
Tyler: Like that just does not make sense to me.
Tyler: So I totally believe that these people both care about doing this right and are extremely
Tyler: scared of the developments that they've seen recently.
Tyler: Like I think it is like Occam's razor.
Tyler: Just take them at face value that like there are things that are moving so fast that they're
Tyler: very afraid.
Tyler: And then even the stuff that has come to light in public, which seems to be at this point,
Tyler: like I think the labs are trying very hard to be more transparent about this stuff seems
Tyler: to be like the extent of the like incidents that have happened are definitely concerning
Tyler: enough that like they're like, okay, these misalignment incidents are becoming a bigger
Tyler: thing and then simultaneously the models are getting so much more capable and are potentially
Tyler: about to hit some kind of like crazy inflection point and their capability.
Tyler: It's like not the time to just be like boldly pushing down the accelerator.
Tyler: That seems pretty reasonable to me, but then like the thing that is scary is the potential
Tyler: of a race dynamic.
Tyler: And that's what everyone is trying to ward off.
Tyler: And it's like that also just requires coordination from everyone because, you know, anthropic
Tyler: isn't going to stop and pace and then watch like, you know, some like random AI company
Tyler: in China, like pull ahead of them.
Tyler: If they feel like that's happening, you better believe they're going to put the accelerator
Tyler: back down or even like Google or meta or XAI come out of nowhere and catch up.
Tyler: So that's like the danger of the race dynamic, I think.
Chris: And I mean, like presupposing that this is all true, the danger of this particular race
Chris: dynamic is that it's a prisoner's dilemma, right?
Chris: And it's too important to like rely on other people's altruism to be like, okay, yes, I'm
Chris: going to not develop nuclear weapons or an AI, right?
Chris: And just like to trust that because it is strictly advantageous for them to say no and
Chris: to do it if they think that they will be able to get there first and be able to control
Chris: it.
Chris: Right.
Chris: Yeah.
Tyler: I assume that's the order is if you ever see like somebody who has in their Twitter profile
Tyler: like a like a three slash three and that's their like little shorthand for like I'm choosing
Tyler: the altruistic equilibrium in like the prisoner's dilemma game, you better believe that person
Tyler: is going to rug you as soon as they can.
Chris: Like, yeah, do not trust that immediately, immediately.
Chris: Yeah, it's a tricky problem.
Chris: I think like a lot of these things come down to coordination problems and like, I think
Chris: my cynicism is just that like, even if we did want to, I find it hard to like, I don't
Chris: know that there is an equilibrium there where that's solvable, like, and maybe there's something
Chris: else going on where what they're actually thinking is like, maybe we can pump the brakes
Chris: for a couple of months whilst people are confused and like talking about it, right?
Chris: Which is a perfectly valid strategy.
Chris: But yeah, long term, I think like these these type of coordination problems are very wicked.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: And I it's hard for me to see.
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: I mean, this is something that people have been talking about from like the beginning
Tyler: of, you know, like the rationalists were talking about this 10 plus years ago, when AI was
Tyler: like doing hot dog, no hot dog, you know, so like, it's kind of playing out how they
Tyler: proposed.
Jackson: It's called classification.
Tyler: I do think it's very interesting, the moment the AI is having in terms of the salience,
Tyler: there's like a couple of things that kind of like, all came together at one moment.
Tyler: I just feel like the cultural, like the normie salience is like as high as it's ever been.
Tyler: There was like the hugging face thing that was like national news.
Tyler: This letter blew up.
Tyler: And then this guy, Jacob coxson.
Tyler: Have you guys like heard his kind of spiel?
Chris: I have.
Tyler: Okay.
Jackson: Oh, yeah.
Tyler: Chris, do you want to pull up this this this thing I just sent in the chat?
Tyler: It looks kind of scary.
Tyler: It should just be an image of this of this guy we can pull up a pot.
Chris: Yeah, yeah, yeah, let me find it.
Chris: Let's let's get him live on the pod.
Chris: There we go.
Chris: Now we know what we're looking at.
Tyler: Oh, it loaded better.
Tyler: Nice.
Tyler: Okay.
Tyler: So as far as I can tell, this is Chris's cousin.
Chris: Hey, I have my Duma AI cousin, right from the wrong side of the family.
Tyler: He's from the British part of Chris's family.
Tyler: It's like, well, a guy with a non-American accent and glasses, like clearly he's related
Tyler: to Chris.
Jackson: What a smirk.
Jackson: Chris, can you make that face?
Chris: No, I don't.
Chris: I don't have it in me.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: I'm not glib enough.
Tyler: But yeah, this guy, he basically like quit anthropic and posted a Twitter thing about
Tyler: how he thought that the labs were like gambling with everyone's lives and then he did a bunch
Tyler: of interviews and mainstream media.
Tyler: And like, I think his message really spoke to a lot of people and a lot of like normal
Tyler: people.
Tyler: And I think it's the first time that this like narrative of like AI is existential risk
Tyler: kind of crossed the normity barrier versus before it was more like AI could take your
Tyler: job or like data centers are like evil in some way that I can't quite put my finger
Tyler: on.
Tyler: But this is like, you know, you have this guy who seems like a normal guy saying he
Tyler: quit his job and he thinks that what they're working on could kill everyone.
Tyler: And then people suddenly this message like connected with a bunch of people and it went
Tyler: super viral.
Tyler: So, I mean, that's another thing that's happening.
Tyler: I think simultaneously is like you have people like Dario and Sam and Elon who are all saying
Tyler: we should slow down because things are getting too risky.
Tyler: And then you have this other person, like kind of talking to the general person about
Tyler: how this risk is like a different class of risk than maybe they had thought previously.
Tyler: But I think kind of like sounds very bizarre to some people initially, but like maybe this
Tyler: message is becoming more saturated to like the normies.
Tyler: And then if that happens, I do wonder if there will be like huge implications politically
Tyler: and socially in terms of like backlash against this stuff, restrictions, regulations, you
Tyler: know, some of it could be good, some of it could be bad.
Tyler: If that's what the people want, you know, democracy.
Chris: I feel like this information environment, like there's so much at stake, whether you
Chris: believe in x risk or not.
Chris: And I'm like, I wouldn't say an x risk denier, but I'm an x risk minimizer personally.
Chris: But even like discounting x risk, there's so much at stake that like there are high
Chris: incentives to try and manipulate the information environment one way or the other.
Chris: Yeah, and I just I think it's like it's extremely difficult.
Chris: But I think anyone on the outside to understand what's going on, you know, even like someone
Chris: who's adjacent to it, let alone like the general public.
Chris: So it's going to be interesting to see how it shakes out.
Jackson: Lovely.
Jackson: Thank you, guys.
Jackson: And great prep for by reading the article.
Jackson: It sounds like the pod is generally aligned that there are some dangers the experts are
Jackson: speaking and but it's unclear how how to slow down without losing the most important race
Jackson: of our lifetimes.
Jackson: And okay, boom.
Jackson: Now we cut over to error bore error bore is free conversion problem.
Jackson: Chris resident stablecoin resident error bore expert.
Chris: What's going on?
Chris: You know what?
Chris: You know, what's more exciting than AI ending the world dollar equivalents in a bank.
Chris: Let's talk about that.
Tyler: One basis point on that dollar equivalent in the bank.
Chris: Yeah, literally like one to five bips on those dollars.
Chris: So the sparknotes here is that, as we've spoken about before, not all stablecoins trade equal,
Chris: they trade a couple of basis points off of each other and off of the US dollar.
Chris: And this is because of like, back pressure.
Chris: So when there's too many in circulation, people want to go and turn them back into US dollars.
Chris: And they do that, you know, they go to what's called the desk, where they say, Hey, here's
Chris: one USDT, give me $1.
Tyler: And that's all that's like usually harbor treasures, right?
Chris: It's usually companies are arbitrageous.
Chris: Yes, exactly.
Chris: So it's institutions.
Chris: And the desk will charge a fee.
Chris: And the desk will also, you know, only some people have access to the desk, depending
Chris: on the company, tether famously, only a couple of people have access to this facility.
Chris: So tether, there can be back pressure on chain where more people want to get out of tether
Chris: than into it, which means that relative to other stablecoins, it trades a little bit below
Chris: peg.
Chris: And what Arabor did, because they are a company, they're like a business to business bank for
Chris: crypto companies and for hard tech companies, is they said, okay, like, you guys just want
Chris: to use stablecoins to do whatever you want to do, we're going to guarantee one to one.
Tyler: And a funny combination, it's like crypto and hard tech.
Tyler: It's like the most, yeah, like, how would you describe crypto, like, it's like shared
Tyler: fiction is what they say, you know, and then hard.
Chris: Yeah, yeah, it's a cryptographic agreement between adversaries at best.
Chris: Yeah, so I mean, I mean, that's that that's their market position.
Chris: And they were like, we're going to guarantee one to one tether to any stablecoin.
Chris: And a very famous market making firm called Wintermute, which is named after an AI in
Chris: a famous book called Neuromancer, which should tell you where this is going.
Chris: They were like, well, yeah, I mean, it ends with them making like millions of dollars
Chris: off of a stablecoin.
Chris: Let me spoil it.
Chris: Dude, what?
Chris: No, so they were like, they were like, okay, we can buy tether for 99.99 cents, and then
Chris: we can turn it in for a dollar, and we're just going to print infinite money for the
Chris: duration of this contract.
Chris: And it sounds like they did.
Chris: They haven't released any figures, but I like I don't think, you know, like Wintermute doesn't
Chris: stock like they would have made quite quite a bag.
Tyler: Like Wintermute presumably has access to like the redemption desks, but it's because the
Tyler: redemption desks don't actually redeem at one dollar, right?
Tyler: Because that's correct.
Tyler: A fee.
Chris: That's correct.
Tyler: And I, Wintermute was selling their tether to Arabor, Arabor was giving them a dollar.
Tyler: Now Arabor has like a tether, and then they have to go to the redemption desk and take
Tyler: that haircut.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: They take a basically a band per million, something like that.
Jackson: Jeez.
Jackson: So wait, were they trading like, like USDC or like USDTs for USDCs?
Jackson: Or is Arabor acting like one of the desks and giving them actual USDs for the USDTs?
Chris: I understand with Arabor, you can either get it as dollars over wire or USDC out.
Chris: And it doesn't really matter which one because USDC trades at peg two and only trades closer
Chris: to the one dollar.
Chris: So they would have just been buying as much USDT as they can get and turning it in into
Chris: dollars and then withdrawing it over wire or, or another coin forever.
Jackson: So they're effectively acting as one of those like arbitrage desks that we're talking about.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: But as Tyler pointed out, like just like eating the fee.
Chris: So basically Wintermute was taking tether's fee, which was subsidized by Arabor like forever.
Chris: Right.
Tyler: And like not just Wintermute, like Wintermute is basically a vacuum for the entire market.
Tyler: Like they will buy every single tether for less than one dollar that they could possibly
Tyler: buy.
Tyler: So they're like single handedly, you know, sucking that up in the market and they have
Tyler: the size and the pockets to do that.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: They're single handedly propping up USDT's peg.
Jackson: And Arabor's left holding the bag for guys.
Chris: Yeah.
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: Poor Peter Thiel.
Jackson: I know.
Chris: Paul Pama Lucky, who I believe is the co-founder.
Tyler: Oh, okay.
Chris: I'm just you know, it has a Lord of the Rings Lonely Mountain name.
Chris: So I think we can make some assumptions here.
Tyler: I think that the Arabor like executive suite needs to spend more time listening to Chris's
Tyler: segments on the permanent under pod.
Tyler: They need to like click into some of these YouTube shorts and they could have avoided
Tyler: this whole problem.
Tyler: We should start maybe perhaps in addition to our church of Big One, we should also start
Tyler: an executive training consulting service.
Chris: Yeah, definitely.
Chris: I mean, like what would we teach that just like how not to give away all of your basis
Chris: points to winter mute?
Chris: Like I'm good at that because of experience, but.
Jackson: Well, we'd all teach different things, you know, we have different specialties, Chris,
Jackson: you would teach stablecoin, D pegs, math, Tyler, you could teach how to roast the shit
Jackson: out of your co-workers, your fellow co-workers.
Jackson: And I like how to wear a wife beater to work and not get fired.
Tyler: A Korean market expert.
Jackson: Yeah, right, I'll teach you how you can't capitalize on the gimchi discount.
Tyler: I know the great guys that bad, come on now.
Chris: To the viewers, he roasts us in private.
Chris: Playful banter.
Chris: It's not just on the pod.
Jackson: It's not just.
Tyler: Yeah, I actually act nice on the pod in private.
Chris: I'm quite abusive to these guys.
Jackson: Yeah, every three days or so, just get a random WhatsApp.
Jackson: It's like, okay, I don't know where that shade is coming from, but no, it's just the first
Jackson: thing I thought about that you can consult on, Tyler.
Jackson: Obviously, also the lighting network, Bitcoin, you know, important stuff, the most salient
Jackson: part of my personality is a hater, apparently, according to the AI, at least.
Tyler: I told you I had the last thing in our WhatsApp I said to you, I thought was very, very nice.
Jackson: Thank you.
Tyler: Thank you.
Chris: That's, but that's not what the fans want.
Chris: They want to see skating reels.
Chris: So here we are.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: Roast Chris on the spot.
Chris: Me again.
Jackson: I'm not going to say roast me on the spot, I'd be kind of like masochistic, right?
Jackson: Okay.
Jackson: So Airborne losing money, they didn't read Chris's a blog post about stable coin, D pegs.
Chris: Hopefully they, they patched it up.
Chris: Classic free money exploit, like just a really classic giving away money.
Chris: I'm sure they knew, right?
Chris: Like I'm sure they were just like, yeah, like, you know, an early bank, they're moving fast.
Chris: I'm sure they were like, yeah, we're going to lose.
Chris: Like they knew that we're going to lose money on the basis trade and it's a service that
Chris: they wanted to offer to people.
Chris: What I'm confused about is whether they knew it was winter mute signing up to the bank
Chris: account because the second I see winter mute anywhere, like on a discord server, like it
Chris: as my counterparty in a trade, uh, I freak out.
Tyler: Um, so yeah, you're like, I just got my lunch stolen.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: I'm like, it's over.
Chris: I have to sell everything.
Tyler: Um, so, well, I read their remediation is that they're like, okay, we still offer this,
Tyler: but you have to have like X amount of money and like a count with us or something.
Tyler: Right.
Tyler: I was like, I don't know if winter might be making that much money to make that worthwhile.
Chris: Totally.
Chris: I mean, we'll see if there's a second headline.
Jackson: We'll have our fingers on the pulse of AirBoys continued liquidity draining by the winter
Jackson: mute and yeah, we'll bring it back if, if anything happens, speaking of quick update,
Jackson: is there anything new on the liquid heist?
Jackson: Did, did liquid get all the, all the Bitcoin back Tyler?
Jackson: I haven't checked in on that.
Tyler: Um, to my knowledge, they did not get the last amount back and I think there's a lot
Tyler: of like, like I think block stream is basically suggesting that they're going to have the
Tyler: authorities like try to find who did this and like treat it as a crime, which is completely
Tyler: justified and within their, um, you know, within something that's reasonable to do.
Tyler: I think a lot of people on social media are kind of just being like, you deserved it.
Tyler: Like stop complaining about not getting that one last bit back because you were like negligent
Tyler: and this person like taught you a lesson, which I don't know.
Tyler: I don't really line up with that myself.
Tyler: Um, but yeah, that's, that's kind of the vibe on Bitcoin, Twitter these days, I think
Tyler: is people just being like, you're stupid.
Tyler: You deserved it.
Tyler: Um, not specifically to block stream, I think just to like everyone, just like the vibes
Jackson: I think are pretty putrid quick recap, liquid, a platform owned by the company block stream
Jackson: got hacked like a week or two ago, uh, or like exploited and lost over $300 million
Jackson: in Bitcoin.
Jackson: And it seems like the only recovered 85% because the hackers gave it back and claimed that
Jackson: the remaining 15% was their bounty for finding, finding the, the exploit.
Jackson: And they should be grateful.
Jackson: They didn't keep all 300, whatever million.
Chris: So first rule of on chain finance, find his keepers well-known well, yeah, I hope the
Jackson: block streams got 30, whatever million in the bank to get there, make their customers
Jackson: whole or hopefully it was like 30 million that they had on liquid.
Jackson: So maybe they just take a loss.
Jackson: That's a pretty substantial amount for a smaller business in terms of cash, but also probably
Jackson: not big enough that the, the, the government is going to be like, Oh, we have to find this
Jackson: 35 million.
Jackson: Like it's 35 million kind of a drop into the bucket for if they don't fill the hole.
Chris: I wonder, and my question with these is always, are they going to socialize the losses, which
Chris: is to say, are they going to like say like, Oh, everyone who had Bitcoin here now has
Chris: 15% less Bitcoin.
Jackson: No way.
Jackson: Because then it's like, everyone's pulling it out of liquid, right?
Chris: Or like there, before that happens, it wouldn't be the first time it's happened, right?
Chris: Socialized losses.
Chris: So yeah.
Chris: How perps work.
Tyler: So you're a borrower will still redeem your liquid Bitcoin for one whole Bitcoin though.
Chris: Yeah.
Tyler: I mean, the best way to do that kind of thing is what like Biff and Ex did back in the day,
Tyler: right?
Tyler: Where they basically like created a token that they gave people to like compensate them and
Tyler: then they could sell that token to get like an immediate money back on their losses, or
Tyler: they could hold on to it and hope to get like full recovery over time.
Tyler: And then eventually that token, I think pay people full recovery, and then it started
Tyler: paying out like a percentage of the Bitfinex earnings.
Tyler: I don't think that's like a legal thing to do, you know, Bitfinex is kind of like play
Tyler: by their own rules, but it's a cool concept of a thing that you could do if you weren't
Tyler: trying to comply with US securities law.
Jackson: It's like now you're a shareholder and you get a dividend.
Jackson: Congratulations.
Jackson: Right.
Tyler: There were also rumors that Bitfinex like bought a lot of the tokens that they issued to people
Tyler: like on the cheap.
Tyler: So they basically like, you can think of it as they had a debt to people of the money
Tyler: that they misplaced and then they like gave them a bunch of debt tokens and then like
Tyler: have like look, you know, standing like very low bids to buy back that debt at like low
Tyler: prices.
Tyler: And then eventually that was a great trade for them.
Jackson: Genius.
Jackson: Yes.
Jackson: Financial engineering.
Tyler: Yeah.
Jackson: Cool.
Jackson: Well, now we rotate back very jarringly into AI, if that's cool with you guys.
Jackson: To the anthropic threat intelligence report where anthropic, one of the largest AI companies
Jackson: shared reports or a report of all the threats they've observed over time.
Jackson: Tyler, you raised this one as an interesting topic with some really cool examples.
Jackson: Would you like to lay it down for the squad?
Tyler: Yeah, anthropic released this report that just kind of gave a little bit of like the
Tyler: state of how some like adversarial actors are using their services.
Tyler: So obviously like they keep a lot of logs of the activity that happened and they can
Tyler: use their AI to like look over those logs and find interesting examples.
Tyler: And some of the examples that they gave were like quite comical or just like like kind
Tyler: of like, wow, like jaw dropping.
Tyler: But I think a lot of the best ones came from this dynamic where they alleged that like
Tyler: specifically moonshot, which does Kimmy and deep seek would literally route their customer
Tyler: API back to cloud.
Tyler: So you connect to like the deep seek API and think that you were like having a conversation
Tyler: with deep seek, but then they would just find the scenes, connect to the cloud API and send
Tyler: your like queries to cloud.
Tyler: And the reason they're doing this is because like think about they just want to gather
Tyler: training data, right?
Tyler: And they want to gather training data that has like realistic user scenarios because
Tyler: those are going to provide the best like distribution of things that you want the model to get better
Tyler: at the matter in the role world because that's actually what people are using the models for.
Tyler: And then also they want to gather training data of like ideally frontier models responding
Tyler: to those real user needs and how that back and forth happens and they can accomplish
Tyler: both of those by basically just proxying the cloud API.
Tyler: So they're doing this to gather training data.
Tyler: I don't think they're doing it because they're like, we want to pretend to be cloud and pretend
Tyler: to be as good as cloud.
Tyler: I think that they're probably doing something like we send 5% of requests to cloud and that's
Tyler: a cost that we eat in order to gather training data at the volume of 5% of our API volume.
Tyler: But the hilarious thing about that is that like the kind of companies or people that
Tyler: tend to use like the deep seek and like moonshot API tend to be like entities that are not
Tyler: super friendly and might not even be allowed to use like the cloud API.
Tyler: So you have these examples of like random, like one of them was like a Russian intelligence
Tyler: agency was like trying to use deep seek or Kimmy to like work on some classified systems
Tyler: that had like API keys and stuff like that.
Tyler: And then like these a get uploaded directly to the Chinese companies, which would be like
Tyler: a terrible security leak in and of itself.
Tyler: But then the Chinese company is also sharing it with Claude.
Tyler: And so not only did some like Russian intelligence system sensitive information end up with like
Tyler: Chinese authorities.
Tyler: It also ends up with an American company.
Tyler: And then there were like another example of like a Chinese government company that was
Tyler: doing something putting together some surveillance software like track people.
Tyler: And apparently the Chinese government like got really mad at moonshot deep seek for doing
Tyler: this because they were like, we didn't expect that you would be sending our queries to America.
Tyler: Like we don't want that.
Jackson: Oh my God.
Chris: Oh my God.
Tyler: Yeah.
Jackson: So now Claude is a spy on accident reporting on the reluctant spy.
Tyler: So I just thought it was super interesting.
Tyler: It shows you like who are using some of those kind of like weirdo company like open open
Tyler: model APIs like, you know, I wouldn't use any open model API specifically the ones that
Tyler: are like overseas.
Tyler: If you could hit like an open model API that's with a company that you have a little bit
Tyler: more trust with like I think those will start to appear on like Amazon bedrock or like in
Tyler: Databricks or in various like places where the inference is happening in the US and like
Tyler: it's with a big reputable company.
Tyler: I would feel better about that.
Tyler: And then if you could specifically use a provider or some of them provide inference on open
Tyler: models in a trusted execution environment and an enclave.
Tyler: And that has cryptographic guarantees around that conversation stays in the enclave.
Tyler: It doesn't leave.
Tyler: There's no logging, all that stuff.
Tyler: That's the way to use those models.
Tyler: I would very, very much not for people who are like, I don't want anthropic or open AI
Tyler: to see my data.
Tyler: Therefore I'm going to use deep seek or moonshot.
Tyler: Like that's the worst option possible.
Tyler: You could use those models in a private way but not through those first party APIs.
Tyler: That's going to have the worst data situation possible for you.
Tyler: And that's the same with like the default on like Venice basically.
Tyler: Like I remember we covered that and it's like Venice, the private AI provider, they offer
Tyler: like a free tier and it provides like no privacy at all.
Tyler: I don't even know who's doing their inference.
Tyler: So like depending on who they picked, it's like really bad or it's just like a little
Tyler: bit of trust in Venice or it's trust in whoever they outsource it to.
Tyler: And then they have some tiers where you do get that cryptographic assurance, which is
Tyler: what you'd want in that scenario.
Tyler: So this is something that you also see with like open code or like open router.
Tyler: Sometimes they offer like free like trials of models.
Tyler: It's like, this is a mystery model and like use for free for two weeks.
Chris: It's called Union alpha, I think just for the audience in case you want to give your
Chris: daughter away to 17 different countries.
Tyler: That's a probably a good way to share like the entire contents of my computer and life
Tyler: with this mystery entity.
Tyler: That sounds like a great idea.
Tyler: Yeah, don't do that with anything remotely sensitive.
Jackson: It's almost like they need, you need like a proof of model.
Jackson: Like you want the response to have like a stamp, stamped by Kimmy K3 or stamped by whatever
Jackson: Claude.
Jackson: You want the cryptographic attestation, bro.
Jackson: The crossover.
Tyler: That's your state.
Jackson: Also, I had to look it up, but moonshot is like the same company that makes Kimmy.
Jackson: Is that right?
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: So they're using the data they're collecting.
Jackson: They're not selling it to somebody else.
Tyler: Yeah, I mean, nothing's stopping them from selling it.
Tyler: Maybe they all pool data.
Tyler: All these companies, they want to like rising tide lifts all boats and they see it as they're
Tyler: all fighting against the American labs.
Tyler: That wouldn't surprise me, but like, yeah, they're definitely getting the data, whether
Tyler: they share it more broadly is possible.
Chris: On OpenRouter, there is a ZDR or ZDR for the American listeners toggle, which stands for
Chris: zero data retention.
Chris: And I'm skeptical of that, but you can at least if you are using OpenRouter, choose
Chris: the providers that you're comfortable with.
Chris: So like I use like Kimmy K3 through an American hosting company, for example.
Chris: It's not fantastic, but at least like it's highly unlikely that the data is going to
Chris: two places and that I'm also getting clawed on the backend, which would be awkward because
Chris: I'm auditing smart contracts.
Tyler: Yeah, I do think that I don't know what that toggle does.
Tyler: Does it mean the OpenRouter isn't retaining data?
Tyler: Does it also mean the provider?
Tyler: I would assume that for it to hold teeth, it would have to mean both of those because
Chris: like there's two parties there.
Chris: They're claiming that they have a ZDR, ZDR arrangement with those providers, right?
Chris: So the providers have promised not to retain data, but at the end of the day, it's not
Chris: a T, right?
Chris: It's not a cryptographic guarantee.
Jackson: So yeah, I think he's not too, not too bad.
Jackson: We're still, we're going even further down on the 1350 on the per Japanese yen and shambles,
Jackson: family chickies cheaper than ever and USD denominated terms.
Chris: How Shibuya Tua is looking better and better.
Chris: So Shibuya Linings.
Tyler: It's an investment in our future.
Jackson: I don't want to deviate too far from the pod, but I think about Japan like at least every
Jackson: other day, maybe because my primary media consumption is anime.
Jackson: And I just think about how delicious and cheap the food is.
Jackson: And I wonder how anyone can live in any country other than Japan after visiting because eating
Jackson: is like something you do three, three, four or five times a day, and you could be eating
Jackson: good and cheap, but instead you're eating bad and expensive wherever you're living.
Jackson: That's not Japan.
Jackson: So I just wanted to share that the food was good.
Chris: I had, I had a, I had a less obsessive experience, but I did like it.
Jackson: It was great.
Tyler: We're really currying favor with our Japanese listeners.
Jackson: We're just going to praise your country for like a few minutes, but it's actually completely
Jackson: authentic.
Jackson: It is.
Chris: And also like, it would be cool to be like a eighties hair metal huge in Japan level
Chris: of fame, I think.
Tyler: So if we can go into that, yeah, it's kind of envisioning, like, you know, you see like
Tyler: the old footage of the Beatles, like visiting Japan, I guess I'm mostly thinking of the
Tyler: one where they visit Shea stadium in the US, but like, I'm sure that happened in Japan
Tyler: too.
Chris: And that's what I'm saying.
Chris: Yeah, that's totally not a grandiose vision for us, by the way, totally normal under pod
Chris: mania.
Jackson: It's be out of dream big, Chris, come on, we're, you know, we're, we're going to get,
Jackson: we're going to get somewhere a hundred percent to the rock stores of the podcast world.
Jackson: All right, we're going to try to cover one more, one more topic here.
Jackson: And that is a mixture of muse payments or muse and secure enclaves.
Jackson: Chris has done some research and secure enclaves, which is a cool technical concept.
Jackson: And it pairs well with metas new release muse.
Jackson: Without further ado, Chris, please.
Jackson: How does muse have to do with secure enclaves?
Jackson: What are secure enclaves?
Jackson: What is muse?
Jackson: Tell us everything.
Chris: All right, so muse, like, like, so full disclosure, I'm not like a big muse user, I used muse
Chris: for the first time a couple of hours ago, but I've used muse, used muse, but I've used
Chris: similar products.
Chris: There's one called instinct.
Chris: And basically they're like AI personal assistants.
Chris: I think like there have been a lot of runs at this.
Chris: I think right now they're really good.
Chris: I don't know if it's model capability or payment integration or all of the above that have
Chris: like really started to make them quite good.
Chris: But like I bought a pair of new balances with muse like an hour ago, and it was fine.
Chris: So yeah, basically muse is this, did they advertise them to you?
Chris: Actually shockingly not.
Chris: But I knew I knew what I wanted.
Chris: I was just like, I would like you to purchase exactly this.
Tyler: You saw new balances on Instagram, and then you bought them on muse.
Chris: No, I'm all my friends told me about them.
Jackson: Your friends saw them on Instagram and then told you about them.
Jackson: They almost certainly did.
Chris: So yeah, I mean, like, it's great, you know, it's a personal assistant.
Chris: It can read your emails.
Chris: It can do things for you.
Chris: It can book appointments.
Chris: I think obviously can purchase things for you.
Tyler: How much access to your personal life did you give it upfront because I think it's like
Tyler: a weird dynamic where obviously the usefulness compounds with how much of like the open kimono
Tyler: kind of life that you adopt and I'm not ready to go full open kimono.
Chris: That was good.
Jackson: I love that metaphor.
Jackson: I left my kimono in Berkeley.
Chris: So I actually hooked all of my Google suite up to a competitor called Instinct because
Chris: I thought that it would be nicer for like a 16 year old intern to be seeing all of my
Chris: personal documents than Mark Zuckerberg, which in hindsight, like kind of a gamble, but it
Chris: felt right at the time.
Chris: And yeah, you're totally right.
Chris: I think there's just like no real privacy guarantees with any of these at the moment.
Chris: Like Instinct didn't advertise any, but Muse made a big deal of doing two things.
Chris: One they hired Moxie Mullinspike, who's a famous cyberpunk who came up with, I think
Chris: he either came up or was one of the first to implement double graduate Diffie Hellman
Chris: and more importantly, signal the app that everybody uses.
Chris: And two, they said that they delayed it for a long time over security concerns.
Chris: However, what they shipped was just a VM.
Chris: So their Muse is running on a VM with, you know, basically the machine is a virtual virtually
Chris: easy for someone to shell in and look at yourself.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: So it's a Docker container, which for those at home is just like a way to run processes
Chris: on your computer in like a container, but like not a way to prevent people from accessing
Chris: that container, you know, based on literally any, like any Facebook engineer could go into
Tyler: your container and read the full chat history, access your API keys to access your G Suite
Tyler: in Chris's case or anything else.
Tyler: You hook up to it.
Tyler: All that stuff.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: I mean, yeah.
Tyler: So in terms of like sensitive personal data that Facebook has that probably is like below
Tyler: the median, you know, they just have like everyone's life, but right.
Chris: Which is even like sadder to think about it as for the average person.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: But I mean, so they promised to implement some kind of privacy virtualization.
Chris: It seems like it will be closer to a private or encrypted virtual machine and less like
Chris: a hardware enclave, but I think it remains to be seen how they actually end up implementing
Chris: that.
Chris: But but yeah, at the moment, it's just like, it's out there like you're open kimono in
Chris: the panopticon using Muse.
Tyler: So that's always a difficult sell to me though, like, well, we're going to start this way,
Tyler: but we promise that we're going to like give you that privacy you want in the future.
Tyler: I think we'll get more private independence of that kind of thing is like really important.
Tyler: And usually if you don't start with like the more private, more kind of like risky version
Tyler: of something, then you don't get there.
Tyler: Over time, I think when you're operating in a big company and evolving that product also
Tyler: because it's going to be probably super complex to like migrate all of these like Muse Docker
Tyler: things into some kind of private version and then like destroy the originals.
Chris: And I fear that it would, you know, end up down this route.
Chris: Anyway, you know, there are like a lot of complexities here.
Chris: Like for example, you know, generally when you run software inside of a T, you have an
Chris: attestation because you shouldn't be able to see inside of the enclave, right?
Chris: You shouldn't be able to see exactly what's happening.
Chris: So you have an attestation that is produced by the enclave that says that the software
Chris: that is running there is really the software that you think is running there.
Chris: But in order for that to matter, you need to have access to the software.
Chris: You know, it needs to be like open source or you need to trust the auditor who is doing
Chris: these checks.
Chris: Right.
Chris: Otherwise anything could be right.
Chris: It like a software.
Chris: It could be running in there that exfiltrates your private data, for example.
Chris: Yeah.
Tyler: So yeah.
Tyler: A ZKP over a closed source software repo and your secure enclave that gives you an AI assistant
Tyler: that's private.
Tyler: How many buzzwords did I just pack into that one 10 seconds?
Chris: I feel like Facebook product managers would love you.
Chris: That's perfect.
Jackson: I'm sure that the average meta user is like drooling over the idea of a ZK Rollup on their
Jackson: secure enclave.
Jackson: I don't know if the target meta customer is privacy conscious to begin with.
Tyler: Yeah, I don't think so, but I do think for meta, like that's their weakness with this
Tyler: product of like they're launching this new brand and this new product and it seems like
Tyler: people really like the product itself.
Tyler: But probably the biggest headwind is just that like, oh, do you want to put your personal
Tyler: data in this like Mark Zuckerberg thing?
Tyler: Like that just gives me the ick already done it with so much.
Jackson: Why not?
Jackson: Just keep it going.
Jackson: That's what you already know about me.
Chris: I think this is a difficult time to sell that though, because like language models create
Chris: like infinite surveillance capability, right?
Chris: Like before it was like, okay, I'm giving away my data and it will be used for like
Chris: terrifyingly accurate advertisements.
Chris: But like potentially like it's impossible to sift through the sum total of like human
Chris: personal data and like, you know, create profiles beyond a certain level of sophistication.
Chris: But I feel like language models have brought this to a point where it's like, I think Facebook
Tyler: is kind of like perfected that science with non-language models.
Tyler: Like you don't need language models to build these profiles that predict what people do.
Tyler: They're just training like, you know, like classical machine learning on that stuff and
Tyler: those are amazing at that.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: And that's their entire business is doing those predictions.
Tyler: It's just they just orient it towards trying to predict what you want to buy.
Tyler: Right.
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: But like the same methods I think could be optimized towards any other objective should
Tyler: they want them to be.
Chris: Well, that's like way less comforting than what I was trying to say.
Chris: So thank you.
Tyler: Yeah.
Chris: Skeptic.
Chris: You're like, they don't even, you're like, they don't even need the like magic intelligence
Chris: in a box to like, you know, uh, know everything about you.
Tyler: No, the magic intelligence in a box is just their way of luring more of your data into
Tyler: their box that they can run through the money AI that already exists.
Chris: It's insane.
Jackson: They're broadening the funnel.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: Okay.
Chris: I will say one interesting thing about Muse though is it has integrated Stripe payments.
Tyler: I was going to ask, what's the payments story here?
Chris: It is stripes link, uh, which now is capable of using stable coins.
Chris: So I think that is probably a maybe a case for stable coins here at some point, uh, but
Chris: we'll see.
Chris: Uh, but basically, you know, stripes link is, uh, that, that checkout solution.
Chris: Uh, and it's also like kind of a light wallet, uh, that allows you to pay online.
Tyler: Um, yeah, but it's not necessarily stable coins.
Tyler: Like you could just connect your credit card to it and then your agent will be able to
Tyler: make card payments.
Chris: Yeah.
Tyler: So actually maybe you could be paying like real cipher punks and using open USD on, uh,
Chris: on tempo, tempo, tempo that is 2 billion in real volume, by the way, if they're using
Tyler: privacy zones where your transactions are private from everyone except for the company
Tyler: operating the zone.
Jackson: The thing is that is not the one selling stuff.
Jackson: So if they integrate Stripe link and they, you buy something from a website that doesn't
Jackson: use link using their agent, how does that work?
Jackson: Is it like they buy it and then you pay them through link and then they suck it from that?
Chris: It's a good question.
Chris: I haven't tried, and maybe it just directed me to a vendor that had Stripe link.
Jackson: Um, but yeah, cool.
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: I think that they also have, um, virtual cards through this thing.
Tyler: And so I think that there's a way for these agents to pay with single use kind of virtual
Tyler: cards that are probably derived from your Stripe link credit card.
Tyler: And that kind of lets you have that functionality outside of the Stripe ecosystem.
Chris: That makes sense.
Chris: What?
Chris: Sorry.
Chris: What do you think the play is here?
Chris: Like, what is the play for this?
Chris: Like it's a good product, right?
Chris: Like I like it.
Chris: I liked, I enjoyed using it other than the data thing.
Tyler: I think the play is just to make a very useful consumer app and get people using it.
Tyler: And then like, I'm sure that they get rev share on, on the payments and they're just
Tyler: spending agent, agentic commerce is going to be a big thing.
Tyler: So they want to own the consumer relationship, um, and then they are like an aggregator again,
Tyler: but it's, they're an aggregator of, um, you know, agentic buyers.
Chris: It's terrible.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: They already have.
Chris: Oh, no, you, sorry, Jackson.
Jackson: They already know what everyone wants to buy so they can get the, get the buy side.
Jackson: And you guys have both mentioned you would let an agents, uh, shop for you.
Jackson: So they're just jumping in there.
Jackson: Maybe the best position to, to take up that role.
Tyler: I like how you say that hypothetically as if Chris and I don't have agents buying stuff
Chris: for us.
Chris: I let Facebook buy my shoes, dude.
Chris: Yeah.
Tyler: I have things for yourself, Jackson, kind of feels like a gift when your agent buys you
Tyler: something with your own money too, you're like, ah, thanks.
Chris: Thanks guy.
Chris: You shouldn't have.
Tyler: Yeah.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: You guys are making me feel like an antique guy here.
Jackson: Jesus.
Jackson: Louise.
Jackson: I need to get with the times.
Chris: I did it for the pod.
Chris: I did it for the pod experiment.
Jackson: All right, we got a, we got to close down because we're actually over time.
Jackson: But luckily our purpose fortune is recovered for only going to lose $11.
Jackson: We could have lost 13, which would have been very sad.
Jackson: So thank you yen for, oh, $10.
Jackson: Thank you yen for going in the other direction.
Jackson: Tyler, Chris, do you have anything, any farewells to send towards our fans?
Tyler: Thank you to the country of Japan for being gracious for fortune hosts this week and also
Jackson: gracious future hosts to the permanent under pod tour extravaganza.
Jackson: Sayonara.